games2jolly.com 2014-10-24

# Privacy Policy | Play free online games on games2jolly

**Privacy Policy**

We at Games2jolly.com respect the privacy of our visitors and provide a secure environment to them for a pleasurable and comfortable experience. We have certain online privacy policy in order to provide the above mentioned service to our visitors. By accessing our website you agree to our privacy policy.

We have the rights to modify this privacy statement at anytime without prior notice so check our policy every time you visit our site. 

**Log Files:**

Like many other Web sites, www.games2jolly.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

**Information that we collect:**

Visitors of Games2jolly.com doesn’t need to give any personal information for accessing the site/playing games/downloading games/searching for games i.e.., providing your personal information is not mandatory but if you are interested you can like our facebook page to allow us to inform you about our recent games and updates.

**Third Party Advertising:**

We may utilize any advertising agency to serve you with advertisements whenever you visit games2jolly.com. Even though your details like email ID, name, address, or phone number will not be revealed to these companies, they can still provide you with the kind of ads that interest you, based on the visits and searches that you make in our site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use some information like click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over (surely not your personal information) during your visits to our website and to other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information from your browser. 

We at www.games2jolly.com do not have any control over the cookies placed by third party advertisers in your browser. If you need to know about their policies regarding their cookies you should check the third party ad servers’ privacy policy. 

**Cookies:**

We place cookies in your browser to be of use in many forms. The feature of cookies is provided by your web browser that allows websites like us to transfer some information to your computer for certain online data remembrance purposes which in turn will be used for third party ad providers to display ads with relative with your interests. 

You may turn the flash cookies ‘ON’ or ’OFF’ by using the Adobe Flash Management tool. However we recommend you to leave the cookies turned on. 

**Contact Us:**

To contact us with any queries or complaints, please email us at games2jolly@gmail.com.
